[
  {
    "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849",
    "criteriaName": "Training",
    "questionArray": [
      {
        "order": "Q9_1638272028123-1644581898090",
        "question": "What challenges did you face while using project on Diksha?",
        "responseType": "multiselect",
        "answers": [["Unable to add the tasks/subtasks"]],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [
          { "value": "R1", "label": "No challenges" },
          { "value": "R2", "label": "Initially unable to view the project assiged to me" },
          { "value": "R3", "label": "Unable to edit the project name & objective" },
          { "value": "R4", "label": "Unable to add the tasks/subtasks" },
          { "value": "R5", "label": "Unable to delete the tasks/subtasks" },
          { "value": "R6", "label": "Unable to acess the learning resource" },
          { "value": "R7", "label": "Unable to add the end date" },
          { "value": "R8", "label": "Unable to change the status of my tasks/subtasks" },
          { "value": "R9", "label": "Unable to upload documents/photos" },
          { "value": "R10", "label": "Unable to sync my progress" },
          { "value": "R11", "label": "Others" }
        ],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q1_1638272028123-1644581898080",
        "question": "On a scale of 1 to 5, how prepared did you and your co-facilitator feel to conduct this workshop at the district level?",
        "responseType": "slider",
        "answers": [4],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q2_1638272028123-1644581898082",
        "question": "Mark the agenda points covered in the workshop.",
        "responseType": "multiselect",
        "answers": [["Opening Activity", "Case Study Discussion"]],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [
          { "value": "R1", "label": "Energizer and Norm Setting" },
          { "value": "R2", "label": "Opening Activity" },
          { "value": "R3", "label": "Why work with Parents?" },
          { "value": "R4", "label": "Rating School Status on SMC" },
          { "value": "R5", "label": "Case Study Discussion" },
          { "value": "R6", "label": "Conducting SMC meeting" },
          { "value": "R7", "label": "Recap and Closing" },
          { "value": "R8", "label": "Planning School Level Project" },
          { "value": "R9", "label": "Collecting Feedback" }
        ],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q3_1638272028123-1644581898083",
        "question": "On a scale of 1-5, how would you rate your facilitation of today's workshop?",
        "responseType": "slider",
        "answers": [4],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q4_1638272028123-1644581898084",
        "question": "From the following options, how would you describe the participants' level of engagement in today's workshop?",
        "responseType": "radio",
        "answers": ["Participants participated only when encouraged by facilitators"],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [
          { "value": "R1", "label": "A majority of the participants were actively participating" },
          { "value": "R2", "label": "Some of the participants were actively participating" },
          { "value": "R3", "label": "Participants participated only when encouraged by facilitators" }
        ],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q5_1638272028123-1644581898085",
        "question": "Could you mention/describe one highlight from today's workshop?",
        "responseType": "text",
        "answers": ["gg"],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q6_1638272028123-1644581898086",
        "question": "What type of support would you need to facilitate the next workshop well?",
        "responseType": "multiselect",
        "answers": [["No additional support required"]],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [
          { "value": "R1", "label": "Doubt-clearing session" },
          { "value": "R2", "label": "Guidance from other districts' facilitators" },
          { "value": "R3", "label": "Resources (supporting material, tools to help in planning workshop)" },
          { "value": "R4", "label": "No additional support required" },
          { "value": "R5", "label": "Any other" }
        ],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q7_1638272028123-1644581898088",
        "question": "On a scale of 1-5, how comfortable were you to use DIKSHA application?",
        "responseType": "slider",
        "answers": [5],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q8_1638272028123-1644581898089",
        "question": "On a scale of 1-5, how useful was the Diksha project to plan your district workshop?",
        "responseType": "slider",
        "answers": [5],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q10_1638272028123-1644581898091",
        "question": "Please explain your challenge/s.",
        "responseType": "text",
        "answers": ["bb"],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q9_1638272028123-1644581898090",
        "question": "What challenges did you face while using project on Diksha?",
        "responseType": "multiselect",
        "answers": [["Unable to edit the project name & objective"]],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [
          { "value": "R1", "label": "No challenges" },
          { "value": "R2", "label": "Initially unable to view the project assiged to me" },
          { "value": "R3", "label": "Unable to edit the project name & objective" },
          { "value": "R4", "label": "Unable to add the tasks/subtasks" },
          { "value": "R5", "label": "Unable to delete the tasks/subtasks" },
          { "value": "R6", "label": "Unable to acess the learning resource" },
          { "value": "R7", "label": "Unable to add the end date" },
          { "value": "R8", "label": "Unable to change the status of my tasks/subtasks" },
          { "value": "R9", "label": "Unable to upload documents/photos" },
          { "value": "R10", "label": "Unable to sync my progress" },
          { "value": "R11", "label": "Others" }
        ],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q1_1638272028123-1644581898080",
        "question": "On a scale of 1 to 5, how prepared did you and your co-facilitator feel to conduct this workshop at the district level?",
        "responseType": "slider",
        "answers": [5],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q2_1638272028123-1644581898082",
        "question": "Mark the agenda points covered in the workshop.",
        "responseType": "multiselect",
        "answers": [["Why work with Parents?"]],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [
          { "value": "R1", "label": "Energizer and Norm Setting" },
          { "value": "R2", "label": "Opening Activity" },
          { "value": "R3", "label": "Why work with Parents?" },
          { "value": "R4", "label": "Rating School Status on SMC" },
          { "value": "R5", "label": "Case Study Discussion" },
          { "value": "R6", "label": "Conducting SMC meeting" },
          { "value": "R7", "label": "Recap and Closing" },
          { "value": "R8", "label": "Planning School Level Project" },
          { "value": "R9", "label": "Collecting Feedback" }
        ],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q3_1638272028123-1644581898083",
        "question": "On a scale of 1-5, how would you rate your facilitation of today's workshop?",
        "responseType": "slider",
        "answers": [1],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q4_1638272028123-1644581898084",
        "question": "From the following options, how would you describe the participants' level of engagement in today's workshop?",
        "responseType": "radio",
        "answers": ["Some of the participants were actively participating"],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [
          { "value": "R1", "label": "A majority of the participants were actively participating" },
          { "value": "R2", "label": "Some of the participants were actively participating" },
          { "value": "R3", "label": "Participants participated only when encouraged by facilitators" }
        ],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q5_1638272028123-1644581898085",
        "question": "Could you mention/describe one highlight from today's workshop?",
        "responseType": "text",
        "answers": ["hh"],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q6_1638272028123-1644581898086",
        "question": "What type of support would you need to facilitate the next workshop well?",
        "responseType": "multiselect",
        "answers": [["No additional support required"]],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [
          { "value": "R1", "label": "Doubt-clearing session" },
          { "value": "R2", "label": "Guidance from other districts' facilitators" },
          { "value": "R3", "label": "Resources (supporting material, tools to help in planning workshop)" },
          { "value": "R4", "label": "No additional support required" },
          { "value": "R5", "label": "Any other" }
        ],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q7_1638272028123-1644581898088",
        "question": "On a scale of 1-5, how comfortable were you to use DIKSHA application?",
        "responseType": "slider",
        "answers": [1],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q8_1638272028123-1644581898089",
        "question": "On a scale of 1-5, how useful was the Diksha project to plan your district workshop?",
        "responseType": "slider",
        "answers": [4],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q10_1638272028123-1644581898091",
        "question": "Please explain your challenge/s.",
        "responseType": "text",
        "answers": ["bh"],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q9_1638272028123-1644581898090",
        "question": "What challenges did you face while using project on Diksha?",
        "responseType": "multiselect",
        "answers": [["Unable to edit the project name & objective"]],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [
          { "value": "R1", "label": "No challenges" },
          { "value": "R2", "label": "Initially unable to view the project assiged to me" },
          { "value": "R3", "label": "Unable to edit the project name & objective" },
          { "value": "R4", "label": "Unable to add the tasks/subtasks" },
          { "value": "R5", "label": "Unable to delete the tasks/subtasks" },
          { "value": "R6", "label": "Unable to acess the learning resource" },
          { "value": "R7", "label": "Unable to add the end date" },
          { "value": "R8", "label": "Unable to change the status of my tasks/subtasks" },
          { "value": "R9", "label": "Unable to upload documents/photos" },
          { "value": "R10", "label": "Unable to sync my progress" },
          { "value": "R11", "label": "Others" }
        ],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q1_1638272028123-1644581898080",
        "question": "On a scale of 1 to 5, how prepared did you and your co-facilitator feel to conduct this workshop at the district level?",
        "responseType": "slider",
        "answers": [5],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q2_1638272028123-1644581898082",
        "question": "Mark the agenda points covered in the workshop.",
        "responseType": "multiselect",
        "answers": [["Why work with Parents?"]],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [
          { "value": "R1", "label": "Energizer and Norm Setting" },
          { "value": "R2", "label": "Opening Activity" },
          { "value": "R3", "label": "Why work with Parents?" },
          { "value": "R4", "label": "Rating School Status on SMC" },
          { "value": "R5", "label": "Case Study Discussion" },
          { "value": "R6", "label": "Conducting SMC meeting" },
          { "value": "R7", "label": "Recap and Closing" },
          { "value": "R8", "label": "Planning School Level Project" },
          { "value": "R9", "label": "Collecting Feedback" }
        ],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q3_1638272028123-1644581898083",
        "question": "On a scale of 1-5, how would you rate your facilitation of today's workshop?",
        "responseType": "slider",
        "answers": [4],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q4_1638272028123-1644581898084",
        "question": "From the following options, how would you describe the participants' level of engagement in today's workshop?",
        "responseType": "radio",
        "answers": ["A majority of the participants were actively participating"],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [
          { "value": "R1", "label": "A majority of the participants were actively participating" },
          { "value": "R2", "label": "Some of the participants were actively participating" },
          { "value": "R3", "label": "Participants participated only when encouraged by facilitators" }
        ],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q5_1638272028123-1644581898085",
        "question": "Could you mention/describe one highlight from today's workshop?",
        "responseType": "text",
        "answers": ["bh"],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q6_1638272028123-1644581898086",
        "question": "What type of support would you need to facilitate the next workshop well?",
        "responseType": "multiselect",
        "answers": [["Resources (supporting material, tools to help in planning workshop)"]],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [
          { "value": "R1", "label": "Doubt-clearing session" },
          { "value": "R2", "label": "Guidance from other districts' facilitators" },
          { "value": "R3", "label": "Resources (supporting material, tools to help in planning workshop)" },
          { "value": "R4", "label": "No additional support required" },
          { "value": "R5", "label": "Any other" }
        ],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q7_1638272028123-1644581898088",
        "question": "On a scale of 1-5, how comfortable were you to use DIKSHA application?",
        "responseType": "slider",
        "answers": [5],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q8_1638272028123-1644581898089",
        "question": "On a scale of 1-5, how useful was the Diksha project to plan your district workshop?",
        "responseType": "slider",
        "answers": [5],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q10_1638272028123-1644581898091",
        "question": "Please explain your challenge/s.",
        "responseType": "text",
        "answers": ["bj"],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q9_1638272028123-1644581898090",
        "question": "What challenges did you face while using project on Diksha?",
        "responseType": "multiselect",
        "answers": [["Unable to add the tasks/subtasks", "Unable to add the end date"]],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [
          { "value": "R1", "label": "No challenges" },
          { "value": "R2", "label": "Initially unable to view the project assiged to me" },
          { "value": "R3", "label": "Unable to edit the project name & objective" },
          { "value": "R4", "label": "Unable to add the tasks/subtasks" },
          { "value": "R5", "label": "Unable to delete the tasks/subtasks" },
          { "value": "R6", "label": "Unable to acess the learning resource" },
          { "value": "R7", "label": "Unable to add the end date" },
          { "value": "R8", "label": "Unable to change the status of my tasks/subtasks" },
          { "value": "R9", "label": "Unable to upload documents/photos" },
          { "value": "R10", "label": "Unable to sync my progress" },
          { "value": "R11", "label": "Others" }
        ],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q1_1638272028123-1644581898080",
        "question": "On a scale of 1 to 5, how prepared did you and your co-facilitator feel to conduct this workshop at the district level?",
        "responseType": "slider",
        "answers": [4],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q2_1638272028123-1644581898082",
        "question": "Mark the agenda points covered in the workshop.",
        "responseType": "multiselect",
        "answers": [["Case Study Discussion", "Why work with Parents?"]],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [
          { "value": "R1", "label": "Energizer and Norm Setting" },
          { "value": "R2", "label": "Opening Activity" },
          { "value": "R3", "label": "Why work with Parents?" },
          { "value": "R4", "label": "Rating School Status on SMC" },
          { "value": "R5", "label": "Case Study Discussion" },
          { "value": "R6", "label": "Conducting SMC meeting" },
          { "value": "R7", "label": "Recap and Closing" },
          { "value": "R8", "label": "Planning School Level Project" },
          { "value": "R9", "label": "Collecting Feedback" }
        ],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q3_1638272028123-1644581898083",
        "question": "On a scale of 1-5, how would you rate your facilitation of today's workshop?",
        "responseType": "slider",
        "answers": [5],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q4_1638272028123-1644581898084",
        "question": "From the following options, how would you describe the participants' level of engagement in today's workshop?",
        "responseType": "radio",
        "answers": ["Some of the participants were actively participating"],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [
          { "value": "R1", "label": "A majority of the participants were actively participating" },
          { "value": "R2", "label": "Some of the participants were actively participating" },
          { "value": "R3", "label": "Participants participated only when encouraged by facilitators" }
        ],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q5_1638272028123-1644581898085",
        "question": "Could you mention/describe one highlight from today's workshop?",
        "responseType": "text",
        "answers": ["bh"],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q6_1638272028123-1644581898086",
        "question": "What type of support would you need to facilitate the next workshop well?",
        "responseType": "multiselect",
        "answers": [["No additional support required"]],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [
          { "value": "R1", "label": "Doubt-clearing session" },
          { "value": "R2", "label": "Guidance from other districts' facilitators" },
          { "value": "R3", "label": "Resources (supporting material, tools to help in planning workshop)" },
          { "value": "R4", "label": "No additional support required" },
          { "value": "R5", "label": "Any other" }
        ],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q7_1638272028123-1644581898088",
        "question": "On a scale of 1-5, how comfortable were you to use DIKSHA application?",
        "responseType": "slider",
        "answers": [4],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q8_1638272028123-1644581898089",
        "question": "On a scale of 1-5, how useful was the Diksha project to plan your district workshop?",
        "responseType": "slider",
        "answers": [4],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q10_1638272028123-1644581898091",
        "question": "Please explain your challenge/s.",
        "responseType": "text",
        "answers": ["bj"],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q9_1638272028123-1644581898090",
        "question": "What challenges did you face while using project on Diksha?",
        "responseType": "multiselect",
        "answers": [["Unable to add the tasks/subtasks"]],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [
          { "value": "R1", "label": "No challenges" },
          { "value": "R2", "label": "Initially unable to view the project assiged to me" },
          { "value": "R3", "label": "Unable to edit the project name & objective" },
          { "value": "R4", "label": "Unable to add the tasks/subtasks" },
          { "value": "R5", "label": "Unable to delete the tasks/subtasks" },
          { "value": "R6", "label": "Unable to acess the learning resource" },
          { "value": "R7", "label": "Unable to add the end date" },
          { "value": "R8", "label": "Unable to change the status of my tasks/subtasks" },
          { "value": "R9", "label": "Unable to upload documents/photos" },
          { "value": "R10", "label": "Unable to sync my progress" },
          { "value": "R11", "label": "Others" }
        ],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q1_1638272028123-1644581898080",
        "question": "On a scale of 1 to 5, how prepared did you and your co-facilitator feel to conduct this workshop at the district level?",
        "responseType": "slider",
        "answers": [5],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q2_1638272028123-1644581898082",
        "question": "Mark the agenda points covered in the workshop.",
        "responseType": "multiselect",
        "answers": [["Why work with Parents?"]],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [
          { "value": "R1", "label": "Energizer and Norm Setting" },
          { "value": "R2", "label": "Opening Activity" },
          { "value": "R3", "label": "Why work with Parents?" },
          { "value": "R4", "label": "Rating School Status on SMC" },
          { "value": "R5", "label": "Case Study Discussion" },
          { "value": "R6", "label": "Conducting SMC meeting" },
          { "value": "R7", "label": "Recap and Closing" },
          { "value": "R8", "label": "Planning School Level Project" },
          { "value": "R9", "label": "Collecting Feedback" }
        ],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q3_1638272028123-1644581898083",
        "question": "On a scale of 1-5, how would you rate your facilitation of today's workshop?",
        "responseType": "slider",
        "answers": [5],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q4_1638272028123-1644581898084",
        "question": "From the following options, how would you describe the participants' level of engagement in today's workshop?",
        "responseType": "radio",
        "answers": ["Participants participated only when encouraged by facilitators"],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [
          { "value": "R1", "label": "A majority of the participants were actively participating" },
          { "value": "R2", "label": "Some of the participants were actively participating" },
          { "value": "R3", "label": "Participants participated only when encouraged by facilitators" }
        ],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q5_1638272028123-1644581898085",
        "question": "Could you mention/describe one highlight from today's workshop?",
        "responseType": "text",
        "answers": ["hh"],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q6_1638272028123-1644581898086",
        "question": "What type of support would you need to facilitate the next workshop well?",
        "responseType": "multiselect",
        "answers": [["Resources (supporting material, tools to help in planning workshop)"]],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [
          { "value": "R1", "label": "Doubt-clearing session" },
          { "value": "R2", "label": "Guidance from other districts' facilitators" },
          { "value": "R3", "label": "Resources (supporting material, tools to help in planning workshop)" },
          { "value": "R4", "label": "No additional support required" },
          { "value": "R5", "label": "Any other" }
        ],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q7_1638272028123-1644581898088",
        "question": "On a scale of 1-5, how comfortable were you to use DIKSHA application?",
        "responseType": "slider",
        "answers": [5],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q8_1638272028123-1644581898089",
        "question": "On a scale of 1-5, how useful was the Diksha project to plan your district workshop?",
        "responseType": "slider",
        "answers": [4],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q10_1638272028123-1644581898091",
        "question": "Please explain your challenge/s.",
        "responseType": "text",
        "answers": ["bj"],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q9_1638272028123-1644581898090",
        "question": "What challenges did you face while using project on Diksha?",
        "responseType": "multiselect",
        "answers": [["Unable to edit the project name & objective"]],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [
          { "value": "R1", "label": "No challenges" },
          { "value": "R2", "label": "Initially unable to view the project assiged to me" },
          { "value": "R3", "label": "Unable to edit the project name & objective" },
          { "value": "R4", "label": "Unable to add the tasks/subtasks" },
          { "value": "R5", "label": "Unable to delete the tasks/subtasks" },
          { "value": "R6", "label": "Unable to acess the learning resource" },
          { "value": "R7", "label": "Unable to add the end date" },
          { "value": "R8", "label": "Unable to change the status of my tasks/subtasks" },
          { "value": "R9", "label": "Unable to upload documents/photos" },
          { "value": "R10", "label": "Unable to sync my progress" },
          { "value": "R11", "label": "Others" }
        ],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q1_1638272028123-1644581898080",
        "question": "On a scale of 1 to 5, how prepared did you and your co-facilitator feel to conduct this workshop at the district level?",
        "responseType": "slider",
        "answers": [5],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q2_1638272028123-1644581898082",
        "question": "Mark the agenda points covered in the workshop.",
        "responseType": "multiselect",
        "answers": [["Why work with Parents?"]],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [
          { "value": "R1", "label": "Energizer and Norm Setting" },
          { "value": "R2", "label": "Opening Activity" },
          { "value": "R3", "label": "Why work with Parents?" },
          { "value": "R4", "label": "Rating School Status on SMC" },
          { "value": "R5", "label": "Case Study Discussion" },
          { "value": "R6", "label": "Conducting SMC meeting" },
          { "value": "R7", "label": "Recap and Closing" },
          { "value": "R8", "label": "Planning School Level Project" },
          { "value": "R9", "label": "Collecting Feedback" }
        ],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q3_1638272028123-1644581898083",
        "question": "On a scale of 1-5, how would you rate your facilitation of today's workshop?",
        "responseType": "slider",
        "answers": [4],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q4_1638272028123-1644581898084",
        "question": "From the following options, how would you describe the participants' level of engagement in today's workshop?",
        "responseType": "radio",
        "answers": ["A majority of the participants were actively participating"],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [
          { "value": "R1", "label": "A majority of the participants were actively participating" },
          { "value": "R2", "label": "Some of the participants were actively participating" },
          { "value": "R3", "label": "Participants participated only when encouraged by facilitators" }
        ],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q5_1638272028123-1644581898085",
        "question": "Could you mention/describe one highlight from today's workshop?",
        "responseType": "text",
        "answers": ["hh"],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q6_1638272028123-1644581898086",
        "question": "What type of support would you need to facilitate the next workshop well?",
        "responseType": "multiselect",
        "answers": [["Resources (supporting material, tools to help in planning workshop)"]],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [
          { "value": "R1", "label": "Doubt-clearing session" },
          { "value": "R2", "label": "Guidance from other districts' facilitators" },
          { "value": "R3", "label": "Resources (supporting material, tools to help in planning workshop)" },
          { "value": "R4", "label": "No additional support required" },
          { "value": "R5", "label": "Any other" }
        ],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q7_1638272028123-1644581898088",
        "question": "On a scale of 1-5, how comfortable were you to use DIKSHA application?",
        "responseType": "slider",
        "answers": [4],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q8_1638272028123-1644581898089",
        "question": "On a scale of 1-5, how useful was the Diksha project to plan your district workshop?",
        "responseType": "slider",
        "answers": [4],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q10_1638272028123-1644581898091",
        "question": "Please explain your challenge/s.",
        "responseType": "text",
        "answers": ["hi"],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q9_1638272028123-1644581898090",
        "question": "What challenges did you face while using project on Diksha?",
        "responseType": "multiselect",
        "answers": [["Unable to edit the project name & objective"]],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [
          { "value": "R1", "label": "No challenges" },
          { "value": "R2", "label": "Initially unable to view the project assiged to me" },
          { "value": "R3", "label": "Unable to edit the project name & objective" },
          { "value": "R4", "label": "Unable to add the tasks/subtasks" },
          { "value": "R5", "label": "Unable to delete the tasks/subtasks" },
          { "value": "R6", "label": "Unable to acess the learning resource" },
          { "value": "R7", "label": "Unable to add the end date" },
          { "value": "R8", "label": "Unable to change the status of my tasks/subtasks" },
          { "value": "R9", "label": "Unable to upload documents/photos" },
          { "value": "R10", "label": "Unable to sync my progress" },
          { "value": "R11", "label": "Others" }
        ],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q1_1638272028123-1644581898080",
        "question": "On a scale of 1 to 5, how prepared did you and your co-facilitator feel to conduct this workshop at the district level?",
        "responseType": "slider",
        "answers": [5],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q2_1638272028123-1644581898082",
        "question": "Mark the agenda points covered in the workshop.",
        "responseType": "multiselect",
        "answers": [["Why work with Parents?"]],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [
          { "value": "R1", "label": "Energizer and Norm Setting" },
          { "value": "R2", "label": "Opening Activity" },
          { "value": "R3", "label": "Why work with Parents?" },
          { "value": "R4", "label": "Rating School Status on SMC" },
          { "value": "R5", "label": "Case Study Discussion" },
          { "value": "R6", "label": "Conducting SMC meeting" },
          { "value": "R7", "label": "Recap and Closing" },
          { "value": "R8", "label": "Planning School Level Project" },
          { "value": "R9", "label": "Collecting Feedback" }
        ],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q3_1638272028123-1644581898083",
        "question": "On a scale of 1-5, how would you rate your facilitation of today's workshop?",
        "responseType": "slider",
        "answers": [3],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q4_1638272028123-1644581898084",
        "question": "From the following options, how would you describe the participants' level of engagement in today's workshop?",
        "responseType": "radio",
        "answers": ["Some of the participants were actively participating"],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [
          { "value": "R1", "label": "A majority of the participants were actively participating" },
          { "value": "R2", "label": "Some of the participants were actively participating" },
          { "value": "R3", "label": "Participants participated only when encouraged by facilitators" }
        ],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q5_1638272028123-1644581898085",
        "question": "Could you mention/describe one highlight from today's workshop?",
        "responseType": "text",
        "answers": ["hhu"],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q6_1638272028123-1644581898086",
        "question": "What type of support would you need to facilitate the next workshop well?",
        "responseType": "multiselect",
        "answers": [["Resources (supporting material, tools to help in planning workshop)"]],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [
          { "value": "R1", "label": "Doubt-clearing session" },
          { "value": "R2", "label": "Guidance from other districts' facilitators" },
          { "value": "R3", "label": "Resources (supporting material, tools to help in planning workshop)" },
          { "value": "R4", "label": "No additional support required" },
          { "value": "R5", "label": "Any other" }
        ],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q7_1638272028123-1644581898088",
        "question": "On a scale of 1-5, how comfortable were you to use DIKSHA application?",
        "responseType": "slider",
        "answers": [4],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q8_1638272028123-1644581898089",
        "question": "On a scale of 1-5, how useful was the Diksha project to plan your district workshop?",
        "responseType": "slider",
        "answers": [4],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      },
      {
        "order": "Q10_1638272028123-1644581898091",
        "question": "Please explain your challenge/s.",
        "responseType": "text",
        "answers": ["bh"],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [],
        "options": [],
        "criteriaName": "Training",
        "criteriaId": "6206540ab848b30008d3d849"
      }
    ]
  }
]
